这都是我到这儿第十次上厕所了
That was the 10th time I've peed since I've been here.
也是你第十次跟我们说了
It's also the 10th time you've told us.
真抱歉  委屈你们的耳朵了
Oh I'm sorry, it must be hard to hear.
跟你说  有三个宝宝在你的膀胱上
I tell you. It's a lot easier having three babies
跳踢踏舞音乐剧真是享受
playing "Bring in 'da Noise, Bring in 'da Funk" on your bladder!
我真是受够怀孕了
I am so tired of being pregnant.
我唯一的乐趣就是喝咖啡
The only happiness I get is from a cup of coffee
当然它是无咖啡因的  因为我怀孕了
which is decaf 'cause, oh, I'm pregnant!
菲比  你要吃饼干吗
Phoebs, you want a cookie?
太谢谢你了
Thank you so much!
菲比  亲爱的  你的情绪波动如何了
So, uh...Phoebs, honey, how are those mood swings coming?
暂时我还没有这个情况
I haven't really had any yet.
-早啊  伙计们  -早
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
好了  戒指拿好
All right, here's the ring.
我愿意  我愿意  千百个愿意
Yes, yes! A thousand times, yes!
单身派对有什么好主意吗
So any ideas for the bachelor party yet?
在你托管结婚戒指
Before you start hanging out wedding rings
筹划单身派对之前
and planning bachelor parties,
是不是该先决定伴郎是谁
don't you have to decide who your best man gonna be?
哦  尴尬了  尴尬了  尴尬了
Oh, it's awkward. It's awkward. It's awkward.
已经找钱德勒了
Sort of already asked Chandler.
什么  你第一次结婚他就当过了
What? He got to do it at your first wedding.
乔伊  我想你能理解的
Joey, I figured you'd understand.
我和他认识的时间比跟你要久得多
I mean I've known him a lot longer.
拜托啦  罗斯  我没有兄弟
Come on, Ross. I don't have any brothers.
永远都没机会当伴郎了
I'm never gonna get to be a best man.
我结婚时  你可以当我的伴郎
You can be the best man when I get married.
我真的永远没机会了啦
I'm never gonna get to be a best man!
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait.
我让你当两次伴郎  你一次也不让我当
So you'll be my best man twice, and I won't be yours at all?
不是啊  当然  你可以当我的伴郎
Oh, no. Yes, of course, you can be my best man.
那我呢  你说我可以当的
What about me? You said I could.
我都没有要结婚
I'm not even getting married!
这个问题应该由科幻小说作家来回答
This is a question for science-fiction writers.
真不敢相信你居然不找我
I can't believe you are not picking me.
你怎么可以不找我
How could it not be me?
我没要...我根本没...
I'm not even...I'm not even...
好  够了  就这么决定了
All right. You know what? That's it.
从现在起  乔伊  你来当我的伴郎
From now on, Joey, I want you to be my best man.
太好了
Yes!
不过真替你遗憾啊
Shame about you, though.
-别闹  -怎么了
- Stop it. - What?
有个宝宝在踢
One of the babies is kicking.
我觉得那是好事呀
I thought that was a good thing.
不是在踢我  是在踢另一个宝宝
Not kicking me. It's kicking one of the other babies.
别逼我进去收拾你哈
Don't make me come in there!
-早啊  -早
- Hey. - Hey.
有大碗可以借我吗
Do you guys have like a big bowl I can borrow?
有  橱子下面有一个
Yeah. There's one right under the cabinet.
多谢
Thanks.
借这个干嘛
Why do you need it?
我们明天晚上要开大派对  回见
We're having a big party tomorrow night. Later!
-你打算要邀请我们吗  -不打算  回见
- You planning on inviting us? - No. Later!
喂  崔比安尼  给我滚回来
Hey, get your ass back here, Tribbiani!
激素作祟
Hormones.
菲比想说的意思是
What Phoebe meant to say was
你们开派对怎么能不邀请我们呢
how come you're having a party and we're not invited?
-因为是罗斯的单身派对  -所以呢
- It's Ross' bachelor party. - So?
你们是单身汉吗
Are you bachelors?
不是
No.
你们是脱衣舞娘吗
Are you strippers?
不是
No.
那就没法邀请你们了
Then you're not invited.
好啊  行啊   那你们也别想
All right. Fine. Then you're not invited to
参加我们的派对
the party that we are gonna have, either.
什么派对
What party?
菲比宝宝的送礼会
The baby shower for Phoebe.
送礼会
Baby shower?
听起来我就没兴趣  回见
That so doesn't sound like something I want to do. Later!
真不敢相信我们要办派对了
I can't believe I'm gonna have a party.
太棒了  派对耶
So great. A party!
我也不知道为什么
I don't know why.
派对筹划已经进展到买酒这一步了
This is what I got going for the party so far, liquor-wise.
-多买几箱酒   -很好
- Get a lot of liquor. - Great.
好  至于邀请名单
OK. Now, in terms of the invite list,
肯定有你  我和钱德勒
obviously I got you, me and Chandler.
我打算邀请甘瑟
I'm gonna invite Gunther
因为我们讨论得很大声
because, well, we've benn talking about this pretty loud.
我一定会去的
I'll be there.
哦对了  我知道这是为你办的派对
Oh, listen. I know it's your party
但我真的强烈要求限制参加派对的
but I'd really like to limit the number of museum geeks
博物馆怪人的人数
that are gonna be there.
行  这样吧  那就别请那些人类学家
OK. Tell you what. Let's not invite any of the anthropologists.
请研究恐龙的就好
OK? Just the dinosaur dudes.
行  那还得买半打儿童啤酒
OK. We'll need a six-pack of Zima.
嗨  你们在干嘛
Hey, guys, what are you doing?
跟我的伴郎筹划我的单身派对
Just planning my bachelor party with my best man.
好吧  祝你们办得比上次好
Yeah, well. Good luck trying to top the last one.
嗯  我觉得吧  这应该不会是件难事
Yeah. See? I don't think it's gonna be that difficult
因为这次派对不会
considering this one won't take place
在必胜客的地下室举行
in the basement of a Pizza Hut.
我是罗斯  罗斯呀
I'm Ross, I'm Ross.
必胜客配不上我  配不上我
I'm too good for the Hut. I'm too good for the Hut.
我得去接本了
Okay, I gotta go pick up Ben.
看样子一切顺利
Everything so far sounds great, Joey.
总之呢  搞温和一点  明白吗
Just remember. Keep it on the mellow side, okay?
就是一群人聚一聚打打牌什么的
Just a couple of guys hanging out playing poker.
-不要找脱衣舞娘之类的  好吗  -放心吧
- No strippers or anything, okay? - You got it.
-好  回头见  -好
- Okay. See you later. - Yeah.
好好筹划你的温水派对吧
Have fun planning your mellow bachelor party.
肯定会有脱衣舞娘的嘛
It's gonna be strippers there.
他又没说不要找脱衣舞娘
He didn't say anything about no strippers.
他刚才就说过  "不要脱衣舞娘"
He just said, "No strippers."
哦  我就当做没听到好了
Oh. I chose not to hear that.
你看我买了什么  你看我买了什么
Look what I got, look what I got, look what I got!
这种衣服真的有给小孩子穿的哟
Can you believe they make these for little people!
给乡下小孩穿的吧
Little village people.
你看这件  我最喜欢这件
Look at this one. This is my favorite.
太可爱了
That is so sweet.
菲比一定会很喜欢打扮他们的
Phoebe's gonna love dressing them in these.
但到时替他们穿衣打扮的不是菲比
Except Phoebe's not gonna be the one who gets to dress them.
因为孩子不归她抚养
Because she's not going to get to keep the babies.
天呐
Oh, my God,
我们办的是史上最令人沮丧的送礼会
we are throwing the most depressing baby shower ever!
别急
Wait a minute.
除非我们送给她
Unless we give her all gifts
产后可以用的礼物
she can use after she's done being pregnant.
像普通咖啡  龙舌兰酒
Like regular coffee. Tequila!
可以给她买条她一直想要的皮裤
And somebody gets her those leather pants she's always wanted!
她一定会很喜欢的
She's gonna love that!
这到底是什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
你们真以为这玩意儿会让我高兴吗
You actually thought it'd make me feel better?
送我一份两个月后才能用的礼物
To give me something I can't even use for two months?
气死我了
This sucks!
好吧  下一个礼物呢
All right. What's my next present?
没有了
We don't have anything.
-对了  关于那个脱衣舞娘  -怎么了
- Hey, listen, man. About the stripper... - Yeah?
叫得好
Good call!
请注意  我讲几句
A little announcement. A little announcement.
我决定
I've decided
我的伴郎是我最好的朋友  甘瑟
that my best man is my best friend Gunther.
我姓什么
What's my last name?
中央公园咖啡馆
Central Perk?
谢谢你没娶瑞秋
Thanks for not marrying Rachel.
甘瑟  记得拿衣服
Hey, Gunther! Don't forget your shirt.
那是什么
Hey. What are those?
派对小赠品  你看
Little party favors. Check it out.
再声明一下
A little announcement.
只是想让大家知道
Just want everybody to know
我的伴郎人选还空着
the position of my best man is still open.
新娘人选也是
And...you know, so is the position of the bride.
很好
Great.
漂亮啊  哥们儿
Smooth, man.
你脖子上沾到点辣椒
You got some chili on your neck.
谢谢大家  今晚很开心
I just want to say thanks, everyone. This was great!
星期一早上见
See you guys on Monday morning.
-谢了  乔伊  -别忘了拿衣服
- Thanks, Joey. - Oh, hey. Don't forget your shirt.
博物馆怪胎们  派对结束了
Okay. Hey, museum geeks! Party's over.
跟小姐说再见  快点
Wave bye-bye to the nice lady. There you go.
回爸妈的地下室去  好的
Back to your parents' basement. All right.
出来吧  孩子们  来
Come on, boys, come on out. Here you go.
-看这些小家伙  是你养的吗  -是啊
- Look at the birdies! Are those yours? - Yeah.
他们是怎么同意你养鸡鸭当宠物的
I don't know how they let you keep chickens and ducks as pets?
我把鸭子训练得很厉害  看好
Oh, yeah. And I got the duck totally trained too. Watch this.
盯着墙壁
Stare at the wall.
不许动
Hardly move.
白白的
Be white.
你真在行
You are good at that.
今晚很愉快
I had fun tonight.
派对办得很棒
You throw one hell of a party.
多谢多谢  很高兴认识你
Thanks. Thanks. It was great meeting you.
要是我有朋友要结婚
Hey, listen, if any of my friends ever get married
或是过生日  过星期二
or have a birthday or a Tuesday...
那就太好了
Yeah, that'd be great.
那该说晚安了
So, I guess, good night.
除非你想留下来
Unless you want to hang around.
-可以吗  -没问题
- Yeah? - Yeah.
你可以跟我的鸭子玩
I'll let you play with my duck.
跳脱衣舞的
Stripper!
舞娘把戒指偷走了
The stripper stole the ring!
钱德勒  起床  脱衣舞娘把戒指偷走了
Chandler, get up! Get up! The stripper stole the ring!
-什么  -戒指不见了
- What? - The ring is gone!
先让我清醒一下
Just give me a minute to wake up for this.
你把戒指弄丢了  你是史上最逊的伴郎
You lost the ring. You're the worst best man, ever!
伙计  一点都不好笑
Dude, this isn't funny.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我昨晚去睡觉的时候还一切正常
I go to sleep last night, everything's cool.
等我醒来  舞娘走了  戒指也不见了
I wake up this morning, the stripper's gone and the ring is gone!
-你跟她上床了  -废话
- You slept with the stripper? - Of course!
-嘿  你们好  -嘿  菲比  -嘿  菲比
- Hi, guys. - Hi, Phoebe. - Hi, Phoebs
我想说声抱歉
I wanted to apologize if I
我昨天在送礼会上似乎凶了点
seemed a tad edgy yesterday at my shower.
激素作祟
Just the hormones.
-没事  我们  -激素嘛
- No, we... - Hormones.
不管怎么样  我都要谢谢你们  你们真有心
Anyway, I wanted to say thank you. It was so sweet.
你似乎好多了  太好了
You seem to be doing much better. That's great.
-你现在怎样  -很好
- How are things going? - Good.
感觉最近的注意力都在我身上
It feels like everything's been about me lately.
你们最近都怎么样了
So what's happening with you?
我们正在说
Well, actually, we were just talking about
我不去参加罗斯的婚礼
me not going to Ross' wedding.
有那段过住  我可能很难面对
It just might be too hard, given the history and all that.
这让我想起当年流落街头时
This reminds me of the time when I was living on the street.
有人说我陪他上床就请我吃饭
This guy offered to buy me food if I slept with him.
这两件事哪里像
How is this like that?
我想想  的确不像
Well, let's see. It's not really like that.
因为那才算是问题
Because, you see, that was an actual problem.
你这只是高中女生无病呻吟
And yours is just a bunch of high-school crap
没人在乎
that nobody really gives...
抱歉  我只是觉得...
I'm sorry. I guess I just thought...
眼泪攻势来了
Here come the water works.
我已经没辙了
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我打给中介公司  他们说不管
I called the company that sent her, and they don't care.
我打911又被吼
I called 911 and they yelled at me.
如果这都不算紧急事件  那什么才算
If this isn't an emergency, then what is!
我来了
Hey, guys.
我想为昨晚的派对再次谢谢你
I just want to thank you again for last night.
真的好难忘
What a great party.
博物馆那伙人玩得很爽
The guys from work had a blast.
其中有个没参加过单身派对
You know, one of them had never been to a bachelor party before.
还有个没参加过派对
Another one had never been to a party before.
那个结婚戒指
So, hey, that wedding ring.
-伙计  可真漂亮啊  -可不是嘛
- Man, that is nice. - Yeah, right?
我打算给自己也买一个一样的
I was thinking about picking one of those babies up for myself.
要去哪里买
Where might one get one of those?
那个戒指啊
That ring?
我奶奶刚来到这个国家时
When my grandmother first came to this country,
那枚戒指和她背包里的衣服
that ring and the clothes on her back
就是她的全部家当了
were all she had with her.
也就是说那枚戒指是独一无二的咯
So you might say that the ring is irreplaceable.
当然  它是我家的传家宝
Absolutely. It's been in my family for generations.
每个戴上它的新娘都能幸福到老
And every bride who's worn it has lived a long and happy life.
也就是说它是一枚魔戒咯
So you might say it's a magic ring.
是啊  可惜被脱衣舞娘偷了
Yeah, the stripper stole it.
我  我的戒指  我的结婚戒指
My-my ring? My-my wedding ring?
脱衣舞娘偷走了我的结婚戒指吗
The stripper stole my wedding ring?
怎么偷的  怎么会这样
How? How could this happen?
我觉得原因就在于你说了
I think it all started when you said,
"嘿  乔伊  你来当我的伴郎吧"
"Hey, Joey, why don't you be my best man!"
好  没事  我来报警
All right. All right. Fine. I'm going to call the cops.
老兄  我是犯了大错
Dude, I screwed up.
可你也不用报警抓我吧
But you don't have to turn me in.
不是抓你  是抓那个舞娘
Not on you, on the stripper.
这样啊  我试过了
Oh, yeah, I already did that.
他们说等侦破所有谋杀案再说
They said they'd look into it after they solve all the murders.
那就找派她过来的中介公司
Okay, then we'll call the company that sent her.
我也试过了
I did that too.
他们不肯透露她的真名和电话
They wouldn't give me her real name or her number.
他们说我再打去就要报警
They said if I bother them again, they'd call the police.
我说  "你去呀  就说我掉了枚戒指"
I said, You talk to the police, you tell them I'm missing a ring.
那怎么办  乔伊  你想让我怎么办
So, what, Joey? What are you telling me?
我们已经无计可施了吗
That there's nothing we can do?
-怎么会这样  -罗斯  我真的很抱歉
- How could this happen? - Look, Ross, I am so, so sorry.
我们可以再叫她一次
What if we just called her
用假名让她找去我的办公室
used a fake name and had her come to my office?
这主意不错  但我们得先找戒指
That sounds like fun, but we got a ring to find!
你的茶  菲比
Here's your tea, Phoebe.
真好喝
It's so good.
谢谢
Thanks.
-那就好  -你喜欢就好
- Good. - So glad you like it.
怎么了  怎么了  茶是她沏的
What? What? She made the tea.
不是  我刚才宫缩了
No, I think I just had a contraction.
-你怎么了  -天哪
- You what? - Oh, my God!
几分钟前我以为自己感觉到了一次
I thougt I felt one a few minutes ago.
现在才确定之前不是错觉
And now I know that definitely was one.
你不能在这里生
You can't have the baby here.
男生搬走之后我还没消毒
I haven't sterilized the apartment since the guys moved out!
没事  我们能搞定
Okay. It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
我来烧水  撕一点床单
I'm gonna boil some water and just rip up some sheets.
别紧张  可能是假性宫缩
It's all right. It's probably false labor.
接近预产期会这样
They said that can happen near the end.
谁去拿书过来
So just...somebody get the book.
-瑞秋  拿书来  -书  好
- Rachel, get the book! - The book! Okay! Okay!
-《圣经》吗  -我哪知道
- The Bible? - I don't know!
好  很好
All right. Okay. Okay. This is great.
钱德勒  你站到桌子后面
Chandler, you get behind the desk.
但愿她进来没认出你...
When she comes in, hopefully she won't recognize you because...
她怎么会认得你
Well, why would she?
然后你按铃把罗斯和我叫来
And then you buzz Ross and I.
你是冈萨勒斯先生  我是王先生
You'll be Mr. Gonzales, and I'll be Mr. Wong.
民族大融合
Diverse.
有人叫保安了吗
Anybody call for security?
冷静
You be cool.
哪位是甘瑟·中央公园咖啡馆
Okay. Which one of you guys is Gunther Central Perk?
嗨  乔伊
Hey, Joey.
我的戒指呢
Where's my ring?
我过世的奶奶留下的婚戒  在哪儿
My dead grandmother's wedding ring. Where is it?
你还真冷静啊  老兄
Way to be cool, man.
他在说什么呢
What is he talking about?
床头柜的丝绒盒里有只戒指
There was a ring in a box on my night stand.
你一走它就不见了
After you left, it was gone.
-你们觉得我偷了枚戒指  -对啊
- You mean you guys think I stole some ring? - Yeah.
一定是你偷的  少废话  从实招来
We know you took it! Just save yourself the time and confess.
你们是谁呀  哈迪兄弟吗
Who are you, the Hardy Boys?
我用不着偷那个劳什子好吗
I don't need to steal some stupid ring, all right?
我干这份工作一星期能挣1600块
I make $1,600 a week doing what I do.
你们有人赚那么多吗
Any of you guys make that?
嫁给我吧
Marry me.
我不懂  戒指整晚都在我房里
I don't get it. It was in my room all night.
如果她没拿
If she didn't take it,
我没拿  你没拿  那是谁拿的
I didn't take it, you didn't take it, then who did?
我们在想事儿呢
We're trying to think.
我还是没搞明白怎么区分真假宫缩
I still don't get how you know one's false labor.
你有看到孩子掉出来了吗
Do you see any babies?
-你感觉如何  -还好吧
- How do you feel? - Okay, I guess.
我不知道
I don't know.
大概是因为快要结束了  我有点...
I guess I know it's going to be over soon so...
那不是很好吗
But isn't that a good thing?
-你说你受够了  -我知道
- You said you were sick of this. - I know.
通常怀孕完之后
You kno, usually, when you're done with the pregnant thing,
就该当妈妈了
and you get to do the mom thing.
而我却会...
But I'm gonna be...
穿着皮裤喝龙舌兰
sitting around in my leather pants, drinking tequila.
有些妈妈也会那样
Some moms do that.
那样更可悲了
That's even sadder.
我知道自己该做什么
Look, I know what I got myself into.
但他们现在在我肚子里
It's just that now that they're in me,
我似乎很了解他们...
it's like I know them and...
把他们送走时我会很难受
It just won't be easy when these little babies have to go away.
亲爱的  我知道
I know, sweetie.
但这不代表你会一无所有啊
But it's not like you won't have anything.
你会有侄子侄女
You'll have nieces and nephews.
这样其实更好
In some ways, that's even better.
-少来了  -不  是真的
- Yeah, okay. - No, really.
你不必为他们的大学学费缩衣节食
You are not gonna be the one worrying about saving for college.
或在他们不乖时骂他们
Or yelling at them when they're bad.
或在他们吵个不停时喂他们吃药
Or putting them on Ritalin when they just won't calm down.
他们离家出走时
You're gonna be the one they come to
会来找你
when they were running away from home.
他们会跟你讨论性的问题
The one they talk to about sex.
你可以当酷姑姑菲比
You just get to be cool Aunt Phoebe.
酷姑姑菲比
Cool Aunt Phoebe.
我是蛮酷的
I am pretty cool.
你知道还有什么吗
And you know what else?
他们一定会爱死你的
Oh, my God. Are they going to love you!
他们会爱死我的
They are gonna love me.
谢谢你们  再次谢谢你们
Thanks, you guys. Again.
哦  亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
谢谢
Thanks.
怎么了
What?
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
天呐
Oh, my God!
又骗到了  你们真好骗
Got you again. You're so easy!
要是他出了什么事
If anything should happen to him...
乔伊  兽医说手术很简单
Joey, the vet said it's a simple procedure.
那又如何  搞不好会出错
So? Things could go wrong.
你又不知道  要是它没撑过去呢
You don't know. What if he doesn't make it?
-他会的  乔  -可万一没有呢
- He will, Joe. - But what if he doesn't?
他真是只好鸭子
He's such a good duck.
我好担心他
I'm so worried about him!
有人丢了戒指吗
Somebody lose a ring?
太好了  谢谢你  太感谢了
Oh, my God! Thank you! Thank you so much!
鸭子怎么样了
How's the duck?
情况很好
He's doing just fine.
正在休息  很快就可以去看他了
He's resting now, but you can see him in a little bit.
太好了
Great.
罗斯  谢谢你这么好脾气
Hey, listen, Ross. Thanks for being so cool about this.
不  没关系
No, that's all right.
不  有关系
No, it's not.
你找我当伴郎  我却让你彻底失望了
You made me your best man and I totally let you down.
-好啦  这不是你的错  -当然是
- Come on, it's not your fault. - Yeah, it is.
你就不会弄丢戒指  对吧
You wouldn't have lost the ring, right?
你知道吗  罗斯  你最初的决定是对的
You know, Ross, you were right from the start.
他才应该当你的伴郎
He should be your best man.
-不  应该你当  -别跟我争了
- No, you should. - Don't argue with me.
伴郎该由我来选
I get to choose my best man.
我要选你们两个人
I want both you guys.
-真的吗  -真的吗
- Really? - Really?
你俩都应该陪在我左右
Both you guys should be up there with me.
你们是我的...
You two are my...
有一个好朋友就我就很幸运了...
I'm lucky to have just one good...
谢了
Thanks, man.
我去下那边
I got to go check something, okay?
-真孩子气   -真像娘们
- What a baby! - Total wuss.